中央公园 1994年
1994年 罗宾的爸爸带她第一次来到纽约城
In 1994, Robin's dad took her to New York City for the first time...
这里棒极了 谢谢你 先生
This is amazing! Thank you, sir!
是啊 这种增进情感的父子同游是没什么坏处
Wella little father-son bonding trip never hurt anyone.
不过去年我们一起出来打狼那次
I-I did almost die from malnutrition
我确实差点饿死
on that wolf hunt last year...
我必须亲手将你推入将死之绝境
I had to almost kill you
你才能领悟杀戮之奥义
for you to learn how to kill.
纽约城真是极好的诶
New York City's the best, eh?
我倒不是挺喜欢 这里就像是埃德蒙顿
I despise it. It's like Edmonton,
埃德蒙顿 加拿大西南部城市
还少了些艺术和文化
minus the arts and culture.
快走吧 不然赶不上航班了
Come on, we'll miss our flight.
我会跟上的
I'll catch up.
将来某一天 我将搬来这里
One day, I'm gonna move here,
嫁给一个久经世故的大城市人
marry a sophisticated big-city man
他脑后那帅到窒息的秀发
with a sick mullet--
mullet 一种前短后长的发型
一直垂到他的垫肩上
like all the way down to his shoulder pads,
到了晚上
and at night,
还会让我帮他梳理
he'll let me brush it...
到时候我会来挖出这个吊坠小盒
and I'll dig up this locket
作为我们婚礼上的"旧物"
so it can be my "Something old" At our wedding.
西方人婚礼上的习俗
二罗
R.J.!
来了 先生
Coming, sir!
我会回来找你的
I'll be back for you.
2013年
当年 我很不好意思把我做的这些事告诉你
Back then, I was embarrassed to tell you I've done that
不过现在我们既然更亲近了
but we're closer now.
我也不用再对你隐藏我阴柔的一面了
I feel like I don't have to hide my feminine side anymore
只是因为你一直想要一个...
just because you've always wanted a...
儿子 是巴尼
Son! It's Barney!
太好了
Great!
我15分钟后赶到 小巴狗
I'll be there in 15, B-dawg.
汪汪
Woof, woof!
这是我俩的暗号
That's our thing.
呃 15分钟后去哪儿
Uh... be where in 15?
真人激光枪
Laser tag.
从来没玩过 小巴狗会教我的
Never been. B-dawg's gonna teach me.
呃 我觉得这样很好 你和巴尼...
Look, I-I think that it's great that you and Barney are...
是小巴狗
B-dawg.
...和小巴狗建立了感情
...B-dawg are bonding,
但是 呃 你答应过要来帮我的
but, um... you agreed to help me with this.
好吧
Fine.
你把卫生棉埋在哪儿了
Where did you bury this tampon?
那是个吊坠小盒
It's a locket.
抱歉 我老是把这些
I'm sorry, I get all these
小女孩的东西搞混
girlie things confused.
你到底需不需要我帮忙
Do you need my help or not?
算了 蠢得要死
Nah, it's stupid.
当罗宾在寻找她的"旧物"的时候
So while Robin searched for her something old,
莉莉和马修在打包他们的新物了
Lily and Marshall packed for their something new:
莉莉要去意大利做为期一年的艺术顾问
Lily's year-long art consultant gig in Italy.
我还是不愿相信
I still can't believe
我们还是得跟这地方告别了
we have to say goodbye to this place...
哦 我知道 宝贝
Oh. I know, baby.
但这可以被当作我们简化自己生活的好理由
But look at it as an excuse to simplify our lives.
你明白 我们没法带着所有东西去意大利
You know, we can't bring everything to Italy,
肯定得丢掉一些垃圾
so we gotta throw out some junk.
比如说 看这个
For example, look...
我以前的大脚怪追踪记录
my old Sasquatch binders
这个我一辈子都不会扔掉的
that "I could never throw away"
因为我将会成为
because "I was gonna be the guy
证明大脚怪存在的人
who proved the existence of Bigfoot..."
这些必须带去意大利
These are obviously coming to Italy.
而这些手提包
But these handbags?
就拜拜咯
Gonzo.
没门
No way!
这些寄托着我深深的感伤呢
These have sentimental meaning to me.
这些不是你20多岁那会从商店顺出来的吗
Didn't you shop-lift these in your 20s?
是啊 我好怀念那段时光的说
Yes, and I get very nostalgic for that time.
等人老了 有娃了 只能金盆洗手了 多伤感啊
You get older, you have kids, you stop stealing, it's sad.
莉莉
Lily...
只是我们没那么多地方当这些了
we just don't have room for these.
可不 你的大脚怪文件夹倒是可以留着吗
Oh, but you get to keep your Bigfoot binders?
等等 为什么这本只到1999年12月
Wait, why is this one just December 1999?
哦 当时千禧年要来了
Oh. Y2K was coming.
很多人逃到树林里面去
Lot of people took to the woods.
看到了真相
Saw the truth.
好了 马修 我们没时间争论
Okay, Marshall, we don't have time to argue
什么丢掉什么留了
over what stays and what goes.
哦 你知道我们该叫谁来吗
Ooh, you know who we gotta bring in?
好吧 我承认他在这方面是有两把刷子
Okay, I agree he is good at this stuff,
但他真心好臭屁啊
but he just gets so cocky.
他才没有呢
No, he doesn't.
听说你们遇到了一点...
So I heard you guys have a bit of a...
打包困难
packing situation.
现在我同意这是个错误的决定
I acknowledge now this was a mistake.
听着 我是过来嚼泡泡糖顺便帮你们打包的
Look, I came here to chew bubblegum and pack boxes.
现在我没有泡泡...
And I'm all out of bubble...
哦 我的天哪... 哦 天哪
Oh, my God.... Oh, my God.
我给吞下去了
I swallowed it.
这严重不
Is that bad?
12分钟后
好的 谢谢了
Okay, thank you.
好了 戈德史密斯医生说我应该没事
Well, Dr. Goldsmith says I should be fine.
我只需要在如厕的时候注意找下了
I just have to look for it in my stool.
所以正如我所说的
So as I was saying
听说你们遇到了一点...
I heard you guys have a bit of a...
打包困难
packing situation.
老爸\N　　　  　　 老妈\N　　 　　 浪漫史\N　　  　　　　第八季  第二十三集\N
S08E23 Something Old
翻译: @卟哒哒伽马 @小白是憎恶 @Big-Fudge @moonywen文妹\N@KRengine达 @轩然AI简 @纷扬DLL @Mr_Gao703\N校对: @我叫肉鸭鸭 @晒小花
压制: @Big-Fudge\N统筹+后期: 怒TR不愿统筹肉小鸭 怒TR不愿后期晒小花
HIMYM字幕组 倾情奉献
你俩都知道
Now, as you know,
提到打包领域 我也算是传奇人物
I'm a bit of a legend when it comes to packing.
知道×2
-We know. -We know.
至今仍流传着
Tales are still told
我在西班牙旅行
of the time I traveled all through Spain...
为期两周的神话
for two weeks.
无论我需要什么
with everything I needed
我那免提小书包 应有尽有
efficiently packed into a hands-free belt satchel.
当地人惊呼我为
The locals called me...
拥有小书包的多啦A梦
好吧 那才不是什么免提小书包
Yeah, it's not a "Hands-free belt satchel," Ted.
是腰包
It's a fanny pack.
才不是腰包
It's not a fanny pack.
还有在西班牙语 那句话是
In Spanish, El Ganso con la Riñonera
腰包呆子
means "Fanny Pack Dork."
才不是
No, it doesn't.
翻译过来是"整理巧手"
It means "Packer of Great Skill and Merit."
我查了
I looked it up.
意思的确是"腰包呆子"
It means"Fanny Pack Dork."
作为整理巧手界的砖家
And as a Packer of Great Skill and Merit,
我将想你们讲解 如何做到俄罗斯方块般的严丝合缝
I will tell you how to pack with Tetris-like precision.
懂了 看到啥都塞你腰包里
We get it, you pack a lot in your fanny.
言之有理
Obvious yet delightful.
好的
Okay.
下午三点 我有个重要面试
I got a big interview at 3:00
关系到我有没有可能去设计另一幢大楼
about possibly designing another building.
在那之前 如果你们遵从我的条令
Until then, if you abide by my rulings,
我将为你们决定哪些带去意大利
I will tell you what goes to Italy
哪些丢入大三角
and what goes in... The Triangle.
S05E03中有记载
孩子们 你们都知道 百慕达大三角
Kids, as you know, "The Bermuda Triangle"
是我们给公寓门前那块地取的名字
was the name we gave to the curb right outside our apartment,
那里有着让一切化为乌有的魔力
which possessed the magical ability to make any item disappear.
瞬间吞噬
Instantly.
清理中最重要的一条法则便是
The biggest rule for de-cluttering is,
这玩意儿你一年之内是否用过
"Have you used it in the last year?"
没用过的话 大三角里呆着去
If not... Triangle.
一年内你跳过绳么
Have you used this jump rope in the last year?
开什么玩笑
Are you kidding?
我天天早上都跳绳 小子
I hop threads every morning, son!
连跳三个 你就能留下它
Do three in a row and you can keep it.
算你狠 莫斯比
Well-played, Mosby.
下一个
Next!
这玩意儿你一年之内是否用过
Have you used it in the last year?
天 我忘了
Gee, I can't remember.
你是在贿赂我吗
Are you trying to bribe me?
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
拿着
Take it.
大三角
Triangle!
下一个
Next!
哇 你可真是块材料啊 爸爸
Wow, you're a natural... Dad.
你明白 我爱罗宾
You know, I love Robin.
我也算是爱她妹妹
And her sister's okay, I guess.
可这些都抵不上最终能拥有一个
But there's something nice about finally having...
儿子
a son.
一个儿...
A s...
我...
I...
克里斯托利双胞胎 九点钟方向
Cristalli twins, nine o'clock!
现在做回你妈咪的卵子 滚走吧
Now make like your mommy's ovum and split!
极好的生物笑话 小巴狗
Solid biology joke, B-dawg.
汪 汪
Woof, woof!
我承认 对于那种未经训练的新兵
Now, I'll admit, to the untrained eye,
有几条打包条令看上去可能有点武断
a few of my packing rulings may have seemed arbitrary.
《去意大利吧》 进大三角
Let's Go Italy? Triangle.
大三角铁
Triangle...
去意大利吧
let's go Italy.
一套大猩猩服和一顶金色假发
A gorilla suit and a blonde wig.
你们去年有用过这些吗
Have you used either of these in the last year?
嫔妾求你了 金刚嬷嬷
Please, Queen Kong...
若能温柔些便是极好的了
be gentle.
没 从来没用过
Nope, haven't used those.
我觉得这东西根本就不是我们的
I don't think those even belong to us.
好了 这个容易决定
Okay, here's an easy one.
一个用了十年的 还破了洞的豆袋椅
A leaky, ten-year-old beanbag chair
上面满是啤酒和水烟渍
covered in beer, bong water
还有早已风干的吃清凉牧场味多力多滋留下的手指印子
and fossilized Cool Ranch Doritos fingerprints.
去意大利
Italy.
再给大软糖说一遍\N　\N
Vieni ancora per Fudge Grande?
伙计们 这椅子都已经在这儿生根了
Guys, this chair has been here forever.
你们一定得带着它
You gotta take it with you.
-去意大利  -泰德
- Italy. - Ted...
意大利不需要这样皱巴巴 红彤彤 漏洞百出
Italy doesn't need something that is wrinkled, red and leaky,
还外加一股酒精加毒品味的东西
and smells like booze and narcotics.
他们已经有前总理西尔维奥•贝卢斯科尼了
They've already got former Prime Minister Silvio Berlusconi.
完全不知道那是谁
I don't know who that is.
这些都是终审裁决
All rulings are final.
好吧 为什么我们喜欢的东西都放到大三角
Okay, why are things that we like getting "Triangled"
-你喜欢的垃圾却留下了  -比如什么
-and crap you like sneaks through? -Like what?
比如那个重达50磅的老点唱机
That old 50-pound karaoke machine.
得了吧
Come on!
我们02年新年是唱着它度过的 还记得吗
We sang in the New Year in '02 on this thing, remember?
我们就是天命真女啊
We were Destiny's Child!
既然我是碧昂丝
And since I was Beyonce ,
我十分确信最终裁定权归我 所以呢
I'm pretty sure I get final say here, so...
我们可不是你的配唱 小贱人
Oh, we were not your backup singers, bitch,
我们是个组合
we were a group.
不好意思 是你们嫁给了Jay-Z
I'm sorry, are you guys married to Jay-Z,
还是我嫁给了Jay-Z
or am I married to Jay-Z?
带去意大利
Italy.
哇
Wow.
你把那个犯哮喘病的孩子
The way you used that kid having an asthma attack
当做人盾这方法
as a human shield?
真是犀利到让我也无法呼吸了
That took my breath away.
好 那接下来
Yeah. Okay, next,
我来突击 你卧倒掩护我
I'll be point guy and you lay down cover.
-然后我...  -哇哦×N
-So I'm... -Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa...
你的意思说不该让我当突击手吗
are you suggesting that I will not be point guy?
听着 如果迈克尔•乔丹没有伤病缠身的话
Look, if Michael Jordan's healthy,
你还会让斯科蒂•皮蓬去主导进攻吗
you don't let Scottie Pippen run the offense.
迈克尔•乔丹和斯科蒂•皮蓬均为NBA球员
对了 你是加拿大人
Oh, you're from Canada, right.
我该怎么说呢
If... how do I put this?
如果韦恩•格雷茨基健康的话 你不会让
If Wayne Gretzky's healthy, you don't let...
韦恩•格雷茨基为加拿大职业冰球明星
呃
uh...
弗朗索瓦
Francois...
我的意思是 冰球蠢毙了 而且我才是突击手
What I'm saying is: hockey is stupid and I'm point guy.
行吧 要么我是突击手 要么我就离队
Well, I'm point guy or I'm off the team.
你是我至今为止认识的最固执的家伙
Gah! You are the most stubborn human being I have ever met!
那你最好给我习惯起来
You better get used to it...
你娶的可是舍巴斯基家族的女人
you're marrying a Scherbatsky.
你女儿连哪怕是一丝丝的如同你那样的
Your daughter is not even a fraction
又顽固 又倔强 又疯疯癫癫都没有
as obstinate, stubborn and... insane as you are!
狗娘养的 到底埋在哪里了
Where are you, you son of a bitch?!
别看这边 孩子们 她马上要尿尿了
Look away, kids, she's about to pee.
什么
What...?
我才不是什么动物
I am not some animal.
我20分钟前才尿过
I peed 20 minutes ago
而且我很利落地埋好了 因为我可是淑女
and I buried it neatly because I am a lady!
泰德 我们从去年开始就没用过豆袋椅了
Ted, we haven't used this chair in the last year.
因此 放大三角
Ergo, Triangle.
我想我知道你要表达什么
Yeah, I guess I see your point.
我是说 如果你从去年起就没有用过这个豆袋椅
I mean, if you haven't used it in the last year...
哦
Oh!
你正在用
Using it!
带去意大利
Italy!
放到大三角
Triangle!
带去意大利
Italy.
-放大三角  -放大三角
-Triangle! -Triangle!
带去意大利
Italy.
好了 打住
Okay, stop!
每次你把他推到椅子上
Every time he lands,
椅子里就放出托里诺十年的灰尘屁
that chair farts out ten-year-old Dorito dust.
托里诺为意大利西北部城市
就是这个豆袋椅
Yeah, it's the chair.
伙计们 相信我 你们在意大利会用到这个豆袋椅的
Guys, trust me: you're gonna want this chair in Italy.
我...它会有家的感觉
I... it'll feel like home.
好了 兄弟
All right, buddy.
败给你了 带去意大利
You win. Italy.
真的吗 太好了
Really? Yeah.
我们请你来做决断
We asked you to be the judge here
就该信你信到底
and we gotta trust your opinion.
她说得对
She's right.
在我们四处去郊游的时候
And with all the traveling that we'll be doing...
我们可能需要几个
we could probably use a couple of your...
你那种免提小书包
hands-free belt satchels.
你们不是说很挫吗
You said they were lame.
我不得不承认
I hate to admit it,
这听起来还是很实用的
but they actually sound useful.
你能帮我们买两个吗
Could you buy us a couple?
两个免提小书包马上就到
Two hands-free belt satchels, coming right up.
而且不用担心 我会挑最潮色
Oh, and don't worry, I'll get cool colors
这样你们就不会是西班牙习语里
so you guys don't look like
所谓的腰包呆子了
whatever the Spanish term really is for "Fanny Pack Dork."
好一朵 腰包呆子啊
弟兄们 这是我们和他们之间的决战
Men, it's us... versus them.
我们今天的壮举
Our actions here today
将永垂青史
will echo through eternity...
站直了小子
Stand up straight, Kaden!
你们这些废物懒蛆们听好了 我只有一条原则
I only have one rule, you worthless maggots:
我们要互相尊重
We all respect each other.
我只有一条原则
I only have one rule:
每上三个十分女
For every three tens you bang,
给个五分赏一炮
throw a bone to a five.
她们会感激并加倍努力 而且这么说吧
They're grateful and hard-working and let's face it,
有时候你基本上就只想躺着不动了
sometimes you just want to lay there.
这和真人激光枪有什么关系
What's that got to do with Laser Tag?
关系大了去了
Everything!
我们必将夺得胜利
...and we will prevail,
就算激战到天明
even if it takes all night!
小白脸
Tanner.
我四点必须回家
I have to be home by 4:00.
还有谁要提早回家的
Anyone else have any scheduling issues?
对面其他人你们可以随便打
You can take down anyone on their team...
但那个大个子留给我来处理
but I want the big man for myself.
你干嘛和那老家伙过不去
What's your beef with oldie?
他是
He's...
我爹
my father.
老丈人吧
Father-in-law.
闭嘴 小凯子
Shut up, Kai.
等一下
Wait a second...
懂了 看到啥都塞你腰包里
We get it, you pack a lot in your fanny.
言之有理
Obvious yet delightful.
噢 不
Oh, no!
不
No!
这呆子×2
-El Ganso! -El Ganso!
一对骗子
Liars!
你们支开我去白跑一趟
You sent me on a fool's errand.
好了好了 你讲讲道理
Okay, to be fair,
买腰包本身就是多此一举
buying a fanny pack is inherently a fool's errand.
这可是免提小书包
Hands-free belt satchels.
而且你们居然欺骗我感情 除非你们要把这椅子留下
And just for that, I will not move from this chair
不然我就杵在这上面不走了
until you agree to keep it!
泰德 和这椅子恰巧相反
Ted, unlike that chair,
你还真是精力旺盛呢
you, sir, are full of beans.
双关语 full of beans词义同时为装满了豆子 与豆袋椅的豆子都漏出来对比
半小时后你可有个面试啊
You have a job interview in half an hour.
管它妹的面试
Screw the interview.
我就要留下来
I'm staying.
而且听说好像要下雨了
And because the forecast calls for rain...
介 可是个雨衣哦
This... is a raincoat.
巴尼在此
Go for Barney.
嘿
Hey. Um...
我这出了点问题
I'm having an issue.
听着 罗宾
Now, listen, Robin...
这事很急吗 还是可以过会再说
is this urgent or can we talk about it later?
算了 蠢得要死
Nah, it's stupid.
玩得开心哦
Have fun.
再见啦 弱子们
So long, losers!
呃
Um...
你们可不可以把我弄下来啊
Look, can you guys help me down?
我
I... um...
泰德 如果这椅子对你来说真的那么重要
Ted, if this chair really means that much to you,
你怎么不自己留着它呢
why don't you just take it for yourself?
不 重要的是你们留着它啊
No, it's important that you keep it.
为什么啊
Why?
这是我们大学毕业搬过来后
This is the first thing we bought
买的第一件东西啊
when we moved here after college.
刚开始的那一周我们仅有的家具就是它
It was the only piece of furniture we had for a week.
可是现在你们俩
And now you two are
都要搬去意大利了
moving to Italy.
要是我们之间的友谊没有通过
What if our friendship doesn't pass
那个"一年内是否用过"的测试怎么办
the "Have you used it in a year" Test?
如果你们可以扔掉这椅子
If you can throw out this chair...
谁又能保证你们不会连我也不要了呢
who's to say you can't throw me out, too?
那种事绝对不可能发生的
That could never happen.
你又不是椅子 你可是我们最好的朋友
You're not a chair, you're our best friend.
你现在是这么说 但这一年之内什么事情都会发生
You can say that, but a lot can change in a year.
兄弟 我
Buddy, I...
听着 我知道是我有点不理智
Look, I know I'm being crazy.
我只是
I just...
我需要和这椅子独处一下
I just need a moment with this chair.
你懂的 就好好的告别一下
You know... to say good-bye.
我们会给你俩一些空间的
We'll give you two some space.
孩子们 你抓不住已经消逝的过去
Kids, you can't cling to the past.
因为无论你抓得有多么紧
Because no matter how tightly you hold on...
它都已经不见了
...it's already gone.
喂
Hello?
嗨
Hi.
我现在在中央公园的旋转木马这里
I'm at the Central Park Carousel and, um...
出了一点小问题
I'm having a little bit of an issue.
恩 什么情况
Uh, what kind of issue?
这个嘛 还真是说来话长了
Actually, it's a long story...
呃 罗宾 听着 我有一个重要会议快迟到了
Um, Robin, listen, I'm-I'm late for a big meeting.
你那边重要吗
Is it important?
算了 蠢得要死
Nah, it's stupid.
祝你好运
Good luck.
好 已经到了最后时刻了 小强们
All right, here's the bottom line, cockroaches.
胜利遥遥无期
There's no end in sight
而且我们也没有补给
and we've got no provisions.
如果已成定局了的话
If it comes down to it,
我需要一个志愿者让我们剩下的人能够...
I need a volunteer to let the rest of us...
干掉他
eat him.
巴尼队看起来好玩多了
Barney's team seems way more fun.
胡说八道
Nonsense.
每个人都有糖糖吃
Candy for everyone!
好 动物之家队 谁想试试雪茄的滋味
Okay, Team Animal House... who wants to try a cigar?
耶 耶
Yeah! Yay!
我又没有说要拿你的脸或其他什么来当炮灰
I'm not saying we're gonna start with your face or anything,
但真的没人愿意
but is there seriously no one here
牺牲一只手或者一只脚吗
willing to give up a hand or a foot?
我们不干了
We're outta here!
泰德 你怎么来了
Ted, why are you here?
你不是有会要开吗 我都告诉你别来了
You had that meeting; I told you not to come.
你说"算了 蠢得要死"时
You said, "Nah, it's stupid,"
这是罗宾语的"这事很重要"
which is Robin-ese for, "It's important."
大家都知道的
Everyone knows that.
唉 也不是每个人
Well... not everyone.
但你不该翘掉那会议的
But you shouldn't have skipped that meeting.
它重要吗
Was it important?
算了 蠢得要死
Nah, it's stupid.
现在 我的未来丈夫
And yet, my future husband--
那个有的时候惹起事来像极了
who I sometimes fear is troublingly similar
我那难以亲近的老爸的人
to my emotionally unavailable father--
抛下我去和某人打真人激光枪了 噢 对 你没猜错
is off shooting laser guns with, oh, yeah, you guessed it:
就是和我那难以亲近的老爸
my emotionally unavailable father.
噢 别这样啊 这不公平
Oh, come on, that's not fair.
如果你告诉巴尼你需要他的话
If you told Barney that you needed him,
他会立刻赶到的
he'd be here in a heartbeat.
可我不需要告诉你
I didn't have to tell you.
你就出现了啊
And you're here.
你连为什么都还不知道
You don't even know why.
看来我是来挖宝的啊
Seems like I'm here to dig.
是在找这些电池吗
Looking for "D"S?
长话短说吧 我向未来的自己许诺说
Long story short, I promised my future self
这个吊坠小盒会成为我婚礼上的"旧物"
the locket would be my "Something old" At my wedding.
怎么
What?
没什么 我只是很喜欢曾经有这种版本的你
No, I just like that there was ever a version of you
会想象着在婚礼上要有一份"旧物"
who imagined having a "Something old" At your wedding.
罗宾•舍巴斯基 你是个小女生
Robin Scherbatsky-- you're a girl.
闭嘴吧你 你才是小女生
Shut up. You're a girl.
那早就说烂掉了
That's been established.
新情报告诉我们你居然也是个小女生
The new information here is that you're a girl.
等等...那是不是...
Wait... is that...?
噢 天哪 我找到了
Oh, my God, I found it.
好吧
Okay...
这吊坠小盒到底意味着什么
what's really going on with this locket?
我有一些我一直无法确信的东西
I'm gonna admit something that I couldn't admit
找到这个之后 我愿意去相信了
until I found this.
我对嫁给巴尼这件事一直都怀有恐惧感
I've been having fears about marrying Barney.
我是说 在很多方面
I mean, in many ways,
他已经变得成熟 会关心人了
he's-he's grown up into a mature, caring adult...
我要用你的枪干掉你
I'm gonna shoot you with your own gun.
但是我还是不知道他是否已经做好结婚的准备
...but I still don't know if he's ready for this.
我也不知道我是否准备好了
I still don't know if I am.
但如果我能找到这个吊坠小盒
But if I could find this locket--
如果它仍然在这 等待着我
if it was still here, waiting for me
就意味着这个宇宙
that would mean that the Universe
希望我嫁给巴尼
wanted me to marry Barney.
这样的话 万事大吉
And that everything was gonna be okay.
如果它不见了 就像是
And when it was gone, it was like...
我对巴尼有过的的种种怀疑
every doute I-I ever had about Barney,
以及对我自己的怀疑 都被挖出来大白于天下了
about myself, got dug up.
但是我找到了
But I found it.
这样一切都没事了
And everything's gonna be okay.
你临死前想说什么吗
Any last words?
看着你在战场上
You know, seeing you on the field of battle--
无情无义 工于心计 不可信赖
ruthless, manipulative, untrustworthy--
你具备了我想要的儿子的所有品质
you've got all the qualities I would've wanted in a son.
现在我对你说
Now I say to you
我爸爸给我留的遗言
the last words my father said to me:
杀了我吧
"Shoot me already."
或者我们接着玩 如果你想的话
Or we could keep playing, if you want.
算了 蠢得要死
Nah, it's stupid.
好吧 动物之家队 我抓到他了
Okay, Team Animal House, I got him!
出来吧
Come on out!
你是突击手 老罗狗
You're point guy, R-dawg.
汪汪
Woof, woof.
意大利
我爱你们 还是把那个垃圾沙发扔了吧
噢 谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
这是宇宙的暗示
This is a sign from the Universe.
这不是宇宙的暗示
It's not a sign from the Universe...
不 这就是
Yes, it is!
吊坠都找不到了
The-the locket is just gone
你还告诉我这不是什么暗示
and you're telling me that doesn't mean anything?
你明明知道这是个不好的暗示 泰德 你不很吃这一套的吗
You know this is a bad omen, Ted-- you're Universe Guy!
你是怀疑论者
And you're Skeptic Girl!
你不该相信这些鬼东西的
You're-you're not supposed to believe any of that.
也许我已经变得对怀疑论起疑心了
Well, maybe I've grown skeptical of being skeptical.
这就是个暗示
This is a sign.
听着 这不是个暗示
Look, it's not a sign.
你嫁给巴尼是正确的
You're doing the right thing marrying Barney.
宇宙不是在给你什么暗示
The Universe isn't sending you some message.
我们都知道 根据科学
As we know from science,
雨水是水蒸气凝结成液态水
rain is liquid water in the form of droplets
之后在大气层中形成水滴
which have condensed from atmospheric vapor
然后降下来变成雨
and then precipitated.
这不是暗示
It's not a sign.
泰德 你知道这就是个暗示
Ted, this is a sign and you know it.
我是说 宇宙现在正朝我尖叫大喊
I mean, the Universe is screaming at me right now!
所有人中 怎么偏偏就是你
How-how-how can you, of all people,
告诉我要无视这个暗示
tell me to ignore that?
因为寻找宇宙的暗示是很愚蠢的
Because maybe it's dumb to look for "Signs from the Universe."
我是说 宇宙还有别的更重要的事要做
I mean, maybe the Universe has better things to do.
天啊 我真希望是这样的
Dear God, I hope it does.
你知道我有多少关于
Do you know how many "Signs" I've gotten
我该或者不该和谁在一起的暗示吗
that I should or shouldn't be with someone?
暗示的结果又去了哪里呢
And where has it gotten me?
How To Fight Loneliness by Wilco
也许压根就没有什么暗示
Maybe there aren't any signs.
也许 也许吊坠小盒就只不过是个吊坠小盒罢了
Maybe... maybe a locket's just a locket,
就如同沙发不过是沙发
a chair is just a chair.
我们可能不需要
Maybe we don't have to
给每样东西都附上意义
give meaning to every little thing.
也许我们不...
Maybe we don't...
也许我们不需要宇宙
maybe we don't need the Universe
告诉我们想要的是什么
to tell us what we really want.
也许我们内心深处都清楚
Maybe we already know that, deep down.
* 谎言磨砺露寒光 *
Sharpen them with lies
* 无论跌倒在何方 *
And whatever's going down
* 都会伴随你身旁 *
Will follow you around
* 如此把孤单抵抗 *
That's how you fight loneliness...
HIMYM字幕组 谢谢观看
欢迎关注字幕组新浪微博及人人网主页
@HIMYM字幕组